Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - A-D
        - Chemical Brothers - Exit planet dust (disc two), 1995; SR-7755; Chemical Brothers (Box 23)
          Catalog # XDUSTLP1; A-side Matrix # NOT BEING BAD OR NOTHING, BUT... XDUSTLP 1 C-1-1-
        - Cher - Take me home, 1979; SR-7756; Cher (Box 23)
          Catalog # NBD 20168 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBD-20168-AS CP-2
        - Chic - Take it off, 1981; SR-7758; Chic (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7759. Different discs.
          Catalog # SD 19323; A-side Matrix # ST-A-814817-A CM2-2
        - Chic - Stage fright; So fine, 1981; SR-7759; Chic (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7758. Different discs.
          Catalog # DMD 306; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40606-1
        - Chic - Tongue in chic, 1982; SR-7760; Chic (Box 23)
          Catalog # 80031-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-825049-C
        - Chicano - The best of everything, 1975; SR-7761; Chicano (Box 23)
          Catalog # MCA-437; A-side Matrix # MCA 510 W3 B.D.D.
          Universal City, California
        - Chief Party Rocker DJ Mars - I'm a down south n****, 2000; SR-7763; Chief Party Rocker DJ Mars; Lil Jon; Eastside Boys (Box 23)
          Catalog # AV95; A-side Matrix # AV-95-A
          AV8 Records
        - Chill Rob G - Ride the rhythm, 1989; SR-25053; Chill Rob G (Box 23)
          Catalog # WPL 2002; A-side Matrix # WP-2002-A-BRIGHT SIDE
          Wild Pitch Records
        - China Shop - Atomic notions, 1981; SR-7764; China Shop (Box 23)
          Catalog # CR-001; A-side Matrix # CR-001-A1
          Condensed Records
        - Chocolate Jam Co. - The spread of the future, 1979; SR-25054; Chocolate Jam Co. (Box 23)
          Catalog # JE 35746; A-side Matrix # PAL-35746-1D
        - Chocolate Milk - Friction, 1982; SR-7765; Chocolate Milk (Box 23)
          Catalog # AFL1-4412; A-side Matrix # AFL1-4412-A
        - Chuck Chillout - Back into time; The operator, 1995; SR-7766; Chuck Chillout; C-Ya Entertainment Allstars (Box 23)
          Catalog # PW111; A-side Matrix # PW-1110A EUROPA DISK DMM NY USA 12738
          Phat Wax Records
        - Citizen - Sex & society, 1980; SR-7767; Citizen (Box 23)
          Catalog # OV 1758; A-side Matrix # PRC OV-1758-A-2-1-1
          Ovation Records
          Glenview, Illinois
        - City Streets - Livin' in the jungle, 1979; SR-7769; City Streets (Box 23)
          Catalog # AFL1-3429; A-side Matrix # AFL 1-3429-A
          RCA
        - City-Wide Allstars - Division 2, 2001; SR-7770; City-Wide Allstars (Box 23)
          Catalog # TREE #25; A-side Matrix # TREE-025A
          Tree Records
        - City-Wide Allstars - Who's got the love; Music plays, 2000; SR-7771; City-Wide Allstars (Box 23)
          Catalog # TREE 24; A-side Matrix # TREE-024 A
        - Clark Sisters - You brought the sunshine, 1981; SR-7772; Clark Sisters (Box 23)
          Catalog # SOG-132; A-side Matrix # SOG 132-A-2
          Sound of Gospel Records
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Clarke, Dave - Archive one (disc one), 1996; SR-7773; Clarke, Dave (Box 23)
          Catalog # 74321 32067 1; A-side Matrix # 08 56249 20 1A1-320671
          Deconstruction
        - Clarke, Dave - Archive one (disc two), 1996; SR-7713; Clarke, Dave (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7714. Multiple copies.
        - Clarke, Dave - Archive one (disc two), 1996; SR-7714; Clarke, Dave (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7713. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 74321 32067 1; A-side Matrix # 08 56249 20 1C1-320671
        - Clarke, Johnny - Originally Mr. Clarke, 1980; SR-7774; Clarke, Johnny (Box 23)
          Catalog # LPCTO108; A-side Matrix # LPCT 0108A
          Clocktower Records
        - Clash - The story of The Clash (disc one), 1988; SR-7720; Clash (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7721. Double album.
          Catalog # E 44036; A-side Matrix # AL 44036-1A
        - Clash - The story of The Clash (disc two), 1988; SR-7721; Clash (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7720. Double album.
          Catalog # E 44037; A-side Matrix # AL 44037-1A
        - Cliff, Jimmy - Follow my mind, 1975; SR-25055; Cliff, Jimmy (Box 23)
          Catalog # MS 2218; A-side Matrix # MS 2218 31878-1A
          Reprise Records
          Burbank, California
        - Clinton, George - George Clinton Family Series Pt. 2 (disc one), 1993; SR-7715; Clinton, George (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7716. Double album.
          Catalog # ESDLP 189; A-side Matrix # A PORKY PRIME CUT ESDLP 189 A1
          Essential
          Europe
        - Clinton, George - George Clinton Family Series Pt. 2 (disc two), 1993; SR-7716; Clinton, George (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7715. Double album.
          Catalog # ESDLP 189; A-side Matrix # ESDLP 189 C1
        - Clinton, George - Computer games, 1982; SR-25056; Clinton, George (Box 23)
          Catalog # ST-12246; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12246-2-1 A1
        - Cloud One - Funky disco tracks of Cloud One, 2005; SR-7777; Cloud One (Box 23)
          Catalog # LP 4040; A-side Matrix # G-100-4040-A
          Queen Constance Records
        - Club Nouveau - Listen to the message, 1988; SR-7778; Club Nouveau (Box 23)
          Catalog # 1-25687; A-side Matrix # 1-25687 A SH-1 FUTUREDISC Q B-3104-SHI L 20360
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Cocker, Joe - Greatests, 1982; SR-7779; Cocker, Joe (Box 23)
          Catalog # 2486 261; A-side Matrix # 160 2486261 A POLYGRAM
        - Coco - Revolución, 1980; SR-7780; Coco (Box 23)
          Catalog # AVI 6082; A-side Matrix # 010-6082-A RE-1
        - Coco - Love exciter; Dance man, 1979; SR-7782; Coco (Box 23)
          Catalog # AVI-12-270-D; A-side Matrix # 2-28-9 029-2-270-A-RC1
        - Coldcut - Coldcut's Christmas break, 1989; SR-7783; Coldcut (Box 23)
          Catalog # HOTPLATE 8; A-side Matrix # HOT PLATE 8 A1
          Ahead Of Our Time
        - Coldcut - Atomic Moog 2000; Boot the system (disc one), 1997; SR-7469; Coldcut (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-8866. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 1248; A-side Matrix # ZEN 1248 A-1-1-1
          Ninja Tune
        - Coldcut - Atomic Moog 2000; Boot the system (disc two), 1997; SR-8866; Coldcut (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7469. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 1248; A-side Matrix # ZEN 1248 C-1-1-1
        - Cole, MJ - Crazy love, 2000; SR-7784; Cole, MJ (Box 23)
          Catalog # TLX 59; A-side Matrix # TLX59-A1
          Talkin' Loud
        - Collage - Get in touch, 1983; SR-7785; Collage (Box 23)
          Catalog # 60240-1; A-side Matrix # ST-ES-60240-A-1 B-17944-A1
          Solar
        - Collins, Bootsy - Ultra wave, 1980; SR-25043; Collins, Bootsy (Box 23)
          Catalog # BSK 3433; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3435-1-W-1
        - Colon, Willie - The good, the bad, the ugly, 1975; SR-7762; Colon, Willie (Box 23)
          different cover
          Catalog # SLP 00484; A-side Matrix # SLP-00484-A
          Fania Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Colors - Get on down to the music, 1981; SR-7768; Colors (Box 23)
          Catalog # BKD 504; A-side Matrix # BKD-504-A-RE
          Becket Records
        - Commodores - Keep on taking me higher; Why you wanna try me, 1981; SR-7781; Commodores (Box 23)
          Catalog # PR-87; A-side Matrix # PR-87-A-66333-D-15A
          Motown
        - Commodores - United, 1986; SR-8070; Commodores (Box 23)
          Catalog # 422 831 194-1-DJ; A-side Matrix # 422-831-194-1-A-2
        - Commodores - Rock solid, 1988; SR-8071; Commodores (Box 23)
          Catalog # 422 835 369-1; A-side Matrix # 422 835 369-1
        - Commodores - Caught in the act, 1975; SR-8072; Commodores (Box 23)
          Catalog # M6-82051; A-side Matrix # M682S1-E5RS-7514-1-S-03B
        - Commodores - Love songs, 1982; SR-8073; Commodores (Box 23)
          Catalog # NE 1171; A-side Matrix # CBS-NE 1171 A11
        - Control X - The system, 1995; SR-8076; Control X (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-8077. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # VRG-114; A-side Matrix # VRG-114 SIDE 1 S-32039
          VRG Records Inc.
        - Control X - The system, 1995; SR-8077; Control X (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-8076. Multiple copies.
        - Tony Cook and the Party People - On the floor (rock-it), 1984; SR-8074; Tony Cook and the Party People (Box 23)
          Catalog # HM 1134; A-side Matrix # HM-1134-A-RE
          Halfmoon Productions
        - Cookie Crew - Born this way, 1989; SR-8075; Cookie Crew (Box 23)
          Catalog # 422 828 134-1; A-side Matrix # 422-828-134-1-AS-3 G1
          FFRR
        - Die Coolen Säue - Stärker Als Das Schicksal (disc one), 1996; SR-7775; Die Coolen Säue (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7776. Double album.
          Catalog # 08-056265-20; A-side Matrix # 08 56265 20 1A1 294771
          BMG
          Germany
        - Die Coolen Säue - Stärker Als Das Schicksal (disc two), 1996; SR-7776; Die Coolen Säue (Box 23)
          In same jacket as # SR-7775. Double album.
          Catalog # 08-056265-20; A-side Matrix # 08 56265 20 1C1 294771
        - Corina - Summertime summertime, 1997; SR-8078; Corina (Box 23)
          Catalog # 44 78567; A-side Matrix # XSS-78567-A
          So So Def
        - Coryell, Larry - Back together again, 1977; SR-8079; Coryell, Larry; Mouzon, Alphonse (Box 23)
          Catalog # SD 18220; A-side Matrix # ST-A-773863-B
        - Cosmetic - Get ready; Put it on, 1982; SR-8080; Cosmetic (Box 23)
          Catalog # GR 1202; A-side Matrix # GR-1202-A
          Gramavision
        - Covington, Matt - We gotta live together, 1983; SR-8082; Covington, Matt (Box 23)
          Catalog # 3883; A-side Matrix # 3883-A
          April Records
        - Crawford, Caroline - Nice and soulful, 1979; SR-8086; Crawford, Caroline; Bohannon, Hamilton (Box 24)
          Catalog # SRM-1-3792; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3792K-A8
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Crawford, Randy - Now we may begin, 1980; SR-8087; Crawford, Randy (Box 24)
          Catalog # BSK 3421; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3481 LW4
        - Crawler - Crawler, 1977; SR-8088; Crawler (Box 24)
          Catalog # S EPC 82083; A-side Matrix # EPC-S-82083-A-3
        - Creative Source - Creative Source, 1973; SR-8091; Creative Source (Box 24)
          Catalog # SRA 8027; A-side Matrix # SRA 8027 A (R)
          Sussex
        - Creative Source - Rhapsody, 1973; SR-8092; Creative Source (Box 24)
          Catalog # LPSX 6-A; A-side Matrix # LPSX 6 A-1U
        - Creedence Clearwater Revival - Bayou country, 1987; SR-8093; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 24)
          Catalog # FACE 502-A; A-side Matrix # DMB-8748 A-1/7/87
          Fantasy
        - Creedence Clearwater Revival - Willie and the Poor Boys, 1969; SR-25072; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 24)
          Catalog # 9160-8397; A-side Matrix # 9160-8397 A
          Ontario, Canada
        - Criss, Gary - Brazilian nights; Amazon queen, 1978; SR-8094; Criss, Gary (Box 24)
          Catalog # SG 2074 (DJ); A-side Matrix # SG-2074-A-DJ
        - Criss, Gary - Rio De Janeiro, 1977; SR-8101; Criss, Gary (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8102. Different discs.
          Catalog # SG 2059; A-side Matrix # SG 2059 A
        - Criss, Gary - Rio De Janeiro, 1977; SR-8102; Criss, Gary (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8101. Different discs. Promo
        - Cristina - Cristina, 1980; SR-8095; Cristina; Monet-Palaci, Cristina (Box 24)
          Catalog # ZEA 33-007; A-side Matrix # ZEA33007 SA-1C
          ZE Records
        - Crooklyn Clan - Eargasmz, 1996; SR-25058; Crooklyn Clan (Box 24)
          Catalog # AV13; A-side Matrix # AV13-1A
        - Crooklyn Dodgers '95 - Return of the Crooklyn Dodgers, 1995; SR-8096; Crooklyn Dodgers '95 (Box 24)
          Catalog # MCA8P 3511; A-side Matrix # (MCA8P-3511-A-2) MCA-12393
          MCA Soundtracks
        - Crosby, Stills & Nash - CSN, 1977; SR-8097; Crosby, Stills & Nash (Box 24)
          Catalog # SD 19104; A-side Matrix # RE CUT STA-773-875-B
        - Crosby, Bing - Bing Crosby's greatest hits, 1977; SR-8098; Crosby, Bing (Box 24)
          Catalog # MCA-3031; A-side Matrix # MCA 1392 W-1
        - Crown Heights Affair - Dream world, 1978; SR-8099; Crown Heights Affair (Box 24)
          Catalog # DSR-9506; A-side Matrix # T1 DSR 9506 A-
          De-Lite Records
        - Crown Heights Affair - You gave me love; Use your body & soul, 1980; SR-8100; Crown Heights Affair (Box 24)
          Catalog # MK 131; A-side Matrix # MK-131-A-1-1-1 PRC
        - Crown Heights Affair - Dance lady dance; The rock is hot, 1979; SR-8103; Crown Heights Affair (Box 24)
          Catalog # MK-79; A-side Matrix # DDS-400A-CTA-2 T1
        - Crown Heights Affair - Dreaming a dream, 1975; SR-8104; Crown Heights Affair (Box 24)
          Catalog # DEP 2017; A-side Matrix # DEP 2017A IW MEDIA
          Woodbury, New York
        - Crustation - Purple (disc one), 1996; SR-8106; Crustation (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8107. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # JIVE T 401 P; A-side Matrix # JIVET 401P A-1
          Jive
        - Crustation - Purple (disc two), 1996; SR-8107; Crustation (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8106. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # JIVE T 401 P; A-side Matrix # JIVET 401P C-1
        - Cruz, Celia - Only they could have made this album, 1977; SR-8089; Cruz, Celia; Colon, Willie (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8090. Different discs.
          Catalog # VS-66; A-side Matrix # VS-66-A
          Vaya Records
        - King, Evelyn "Champagne" - Shame, 1977; SR-8090; King, Evelyn "Champagne" (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8089. Different discs.
          Catalog # PD-11213; A-side Matrix # Pd 11213 A
        - Cruz, Celia - Only they could have made this album, 1977; SR-8108; Cruz, Celia; Colon, Willie (Box 24)
          Catalog # JMVS-66; A-side Matrix # VS-66-A
        - Culture Club - Waking up with the house on fire, 1984; SR-8109; Culture Club (Box 24)
          Catalog # OE 39881; A-side Matrix # AL-39881-1F
        - Current - Theme from "Rocky" (gonna fly now), 1977; SR-8112; Current (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8113. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # PBD-3-A; A-side Matrix # PBD-3S-2
          Playboy Records
        - Napoli, Jeanne - Let's make love, 1977; SR-8113; Napoli, Jeanne (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8112. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # VI-D 734-A; A-side Matrix # VI-D734-A
          Vigor Records
        - Cure - Close to me (closer mix), 1990; SR-8114; Cure (Box 24)
          Catalog # ED 5513; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66582A-3
          Elecktra
        - Curtis, King - Live at Fillmore West, 1971; SR-8115; Curtis, King (Box 24)
          Catalog # SD 33-359; A-side Matrix # ST-C-712265 A
          Atco Records
        - Curtiss, Cat - Yes I love you, 1982; SR-8081; Curtiss, Cat; Saxton Kari and Orchestra (Box 24)
          Catalog # SUN 402; A-side Matrix # SUN-402-A
          Sunnyview
        - Cut La Roc - Mad skills EP, 1996; SR-8110; Cut La Roc (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8111. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 11; A-side Matrix # SKINT+11+AA
          Skint
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - Cut La Roc - Mad skills EP, 1996; SR-8111; Cut La Roc (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8110. Multiple copies.
        - Cut La Roc - Mad skills 2 EP, 1997; SR-8116; Cut La Roc (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8117. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 22; A-side Matrix # SKINT+22+AA
        - Cut La Roc - Mad skills 2 EP, 1997; SR-8117; Cut La Roc (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8116. Multiple copies.
        - Cut La Roc - Mad skills EP, 1996; SR-8118; Cut La Roc (Box 24)
        - Cymande - Arrival, 1981; SR-8119; Cymande (Box 24)
          Catalog # LP 141; A-side Matrix # PWLP-141-A CY-1981
          Paul Winley Records
        - Cymande - Second time around, 1973; SR-25059; Cymande (Box 24)
          Catalog # JLS 3054; A-side Matrix # JLS-3054-A
          Janus Records
        - Cymone, André - A.C., 1985; SR-8120; Cymone, André (Box 24)
          Catalog # FC 40037; A-side Matrix # PAL-40037-2B
        - Cymone, André - Survivin' in the 80's, 1983; SR-8121; Cymone, André (Box 24)
          Catalog # AL 38902; A-side Matrix # PAL 38902-1A
        - Dakila - Dakila, 1972; SR-25069; Dakila (Box 24)
          Catalog # KE-31756; A-side Matrix # PAL31756-1B
        - Dal Bello, Lisa - Drastic measures, 1981; SR-25060; Dal Bello, Lisa (Box 24)
          Catalog # ST-12140; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12140 F-K B-15695
        - Daniel - Sunbeam, 1981; SR-8130; Daniel; Sahuleka, Daniel (Box 24)
          Catalog # CS 109-A; A-side Matrix # CS109A JW | PRESSWELL 12/28/81 dby/DVG
          City Sounds
        - Danielle - Danielle, 1980; SR-8131; Danielle (Box 24)
          Catalog # NBLP 7210 DJ; A-side Matrix # A-2 NBLP-7210-AS K-2
        - Daniels, Eddie - Streetwind, 1978; SR-8132; Daniels, Eddie (Box 24)
          Catalog # MARLIN 2214; A-side Matrix # MAR-2214-A
          Marlin
        - Dante's Inferno - Ain't misbehavin' (one never knows do one?), 1979; SR-8142; Dante's Inferno (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8143. Multiple copies. Promo
          Catalog # L33-1006; A-side Matrix # INF-16003-A-SS-1
          Infinity Records
        - Dante's Inferno - Ain't misbehavin' (one never knows do one?), 1979; SR-8143; Dante's Inferno (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8142. Multiple copies. Promo
        - Darby, Ian - Break city; Taking the waterfront by force, 1984; SR-8133; Darby, Ian (Box 24)
          Catalog # TE 2; A-side Matrix # TE-2-A
          Telefon Records
        - Darcus - Darcus, 1977; SR-8134; Darcus (Box 24)
          Catalog # APL1-2454; A-side Matrix # APL-1-2454-A-1
        - Darko, George - Hilife time, 1983; SR-8135; Darko, George (Box 24)
          Catalog # LS 72; A-side Matrix # MPO LS-72-A
          Sacodisc International
        - Darko, George - Hilife time, 1983; SR-8144; Darko, George (Box 24)
          Catalog # DA 2; A-side Matrix # DA 2 A1
          Okoman Records
        - Darts - Darts, 1978; SR-8147; Darts (Box 24)
          Catalog # UA-LA850-G; A-side Matrix # UALA 850-1
          United Artists Records
        - Dash, Sarah - Close enough, 1981; SR-8148; Dash, Sarah (Box 24)
          Catalog # FZ 37659; A-side Matrix # PAL-37659-1C
          Kirshner
        - Dash, Sarah - Oo-la-la Sarah Dash, 1980; SR-8149; Dash, Sarah (Box 24)
          Catalog # JZ 36207; A-side Matrix # AL-36207-1G
        - David, Craig - Born to do it (disc one), 2000; SR-8145; David, Craig (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8146. Double album.
          Catalog # 010740WST; A-side Matrix # B038069-01 A1 MK
          Wildstar Records
        - David, Craig - Born to do it (disc two), 2000; SR-8146; David, Craig (Box 24)
          In same jacket as # SR-8145. Double album.
          Catalog # 010740WST; A-side Matrix # B038069-02 C1 MK
        - Davis, Betty - Betty Davis, 1973; SR-8150; Davis, Betty (Box 25)
          Catalog # JSS-5; A-side Matrix # JSS 5 A -2
          Just Sunshine Records
        - Davis, Paul - Tower of funk EP, 1998; SR-8151; Davis, Paul (Box 25)
          Catalog # MUELLER 2016; A-side Matrix # MULLER 2016 D+M
          Müller Records
        - Davis, Rainy - Lowdown so & so, 1986; SR-8152; Davis, Rainy (Box 25)
          Catalog # 44 05997; A-side Matrix # XSS-175641-1A
        - Davis, Rainy - Sweetheart, 1987; SR-8153; Davis, Rainy (Box 25)
          Catalog # FC 40635; A-side Matrix # AL-40635 AC-40635-1B G1
        - Davis, Tyrone - I can't go on this way, 1978; SR-8154; Davis, Tyrone (Box 25)
          Catalog # JC 35304; A-side Matrix # AL-35301-1B
        - Davy D - Davy's ride, 1987; SR-8155; Davy D; Hurricane (Box 25)
          Catalog # FC 40657; A-side Matrix # AL-40657 1A DMM G
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Day, Morris - Daydreaming, 1988; SR-8156; Day, Morris (Box 25)
          Catalog # 92 56511; A-side Matrix # 92-56511-1
          Scarborough, Ontario
        - Day, Morris - Color of success, 1985; SR-8157; Day, Morris (Box 25)
          Catalog # 1-25320; A-side Matrix # 1-25320-A-S 2
        - Daye, Cory - Cory and me, 1979; SR-8158; Daye, Cory (Box 25)
          Catalog # BXL1-3408; A-side Matrix # BXL-1-3408-A1
          New York International Records
        - De La Soul - Eye know (new remixes by SweMix), 1989; SR-8164; De La Soul (Box 25)
          Catalog # FLY 021R; A-side Matrix # FLY 021 R A
          Flying Records
          Italy
        - De Lugendo, Malage - Malage De Lugendo, 1988; SR-25061; De Lugendo, Malage (Box 25)
          Catalog # SYL 8359; A-side Matrix # AM EXP 68-4 S YL 38751-1 A
          Syllart Records
        - De Opels - We have come a long way, 1975; SR-25062; De Opels (Box 25)
          Catalog # GS-7797; A-side Matrix # GS 7797 A
        - Deadly Avenger - Illicit EP, 1998; SR-8165; Deadly Avenger (Box 25)
          Catalog # ILL001; A-side Matrix # ILL 001-A1
          Illicit Recordings
        - Dealers - The Dealers, 1985; SR-8166; Dealers (Box 25)
          Catalog # BFZ 40065; A-side Matrix # AL-40065-1A
          CBS Associated Records
        - DeBarge - Rhythm of the night, 1983; SR-8169; DeBarge (Box 25)
          Catalog # 6123GL; A-side Matrix # 6123-6LA-15A ZFN
          Gordy
        - DeBarge - The DeBarges, 1981; SR-8170; DeBarge (Box 25)
          Catalog # G8-1003MI; A-side Matrix # G8-1003MIA-RE1-15B ZWC #13
        - DeBarge, Bunny - In love, 1987; SR-8171; DeBarge, Bunny (Box 25)
          Catalog # 6217ML; A-side Matrix # 6217-GLA-15B ZAO
        - DeBarge, Chico - Chico DeBarge, 1986; SR-8172; DeBarge, Chico (Box 25)
          Catalog # ZL72524; A-side Matrix # DM B-6265 A-1/10-86
        - Deele - Body talk, 1983; SR-8159; Deele (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8160. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # ED 4934; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-4934-A-1
        - Deele - Street beat, 1983; SR-8160; Deele (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8159. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # 60285-1; A-side Matrix # ST-ES-60285-A-2 B-18641-A2 SLM 5449 SP 0-1
        - Deele - Material thangz, 1985; SR-8175; Deele (Box 25)
          Catalog # 60410-1; A-side Matrix # SLM 9352 1- SH-SP ST-ES-60410-A F-1 0 B-21030-A FL
        - Deele - Eyes of a stranger, 1987; SR-8180; Deele (Box 25)
          Catalog # ST-72555; A-side Matrix # ST-1-72555 F-2 O B-27273-F2 16306-X
        - Dees, Rick - You got those lips, 1978; SR-8162; Dees, Rick (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8163 Promo
          Catalog # D-116; A-side Matrix # D-116-A
          Stax
          Berkeley, California
        - Dees, Rick - You got those lips, 1978; SR-8163; Dees, Rick (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8162 Promo
        - Def Jef - Just a poet with soul, 1989; SR-8183; Def Jef (Box 25)
          Catalog # DV 3001; A-side Matrix # DV-3001-A
          Delicious Vinyl
        - Defunkt - In America, 1989; SR-8186; Defunkt (Box 25)
          Catalog # 90911-1; A-side Matrix # ST IL 886925-DMM A SP 1-1
          Antilles New Directions
        - Dejean, Debra - Are you lovin somebody; You've really got a hold on me, 1981; SR-8167; Dejean, Debra (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8168. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # 4W9 02541; A-side Matrix # 4W9-2541-A-T2
          Handshake Records And Tapes
        - Dejean, Debra - Are you lovin somebody; You've really got a hold on me, 1981; SR-8168; Dejean, Debra (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8167. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # 4W9 02541; A-side Matrix # 4W9-02541-A 1B